Roundlay: PogChamp
Roundlay: Stream is hitchy as fuck
techinicabor: ^
bawdlifting: Yas kweeennn
codevisionary: holy shit
coProof: Yeah I e here George
capjackm: yo!
speeddrawing101: shroud200
NonTrivial778: hiiiiiiiiiii
codevisionary: LINUX FTW
7cking_markopolo: too late for me. its 6:30 am here
dorkmo: yezzzzzzz
cleverclover7: hey
MallocRS: chad hotz
codevisionary: George Hotz Linux = Life
kevczy: Omg dude it’s 11 30 here
un3okapi: cam and audio is skipping :(
shekel_gobblin: logang here ayo jake paulers
tanoshiizo: arch btw
palenwall: wow speedtest 900
zmechs: lower bitrate noob
ivanjelly0313: Hello from Taiwan
bawdlifting: Audio is fine.
un3okapi: the audio is static-y
capjackm: its better now
codevisionary: video frames are dropping as well bro
ckk0t0: What up. All good here
Lothsun: How’s it going George?
codevisionary: is that a Yeti?
fuzzuf: P=NP
codevisionary: nice
ChanceMakerLIVE: This is a wonderful slideshow
quelsarprime: Thailand in da houz
shekel_gobblin: the bitrate is as low as telsa stock jesus mate @georgehotz
codevisionary: LOL @ChanceMakerLIVE
ckk0t0: Rapping? Wtf.
dorkmo: win10
IsaacRamsay: Kreygasm
tanoshiizo: do some freestyle to test it
ahahaitslit: yee boi
NonTrivial778: dropping frames
cleverclover7: very nice
un3okapi: Yeah it sounds great c:
quelsarprime: yeah boy
ziggyzergling: You need to set it up in obs for us to hear?
z0di4ckx: hiii
cjoelrun: pacman it up
JiNJaProductionz: check to make sure OBS is using the Yeti
coProof: Yeh it’s good
Aocuser: It still uses default one
JiNJaProductionz: settings > audio
Santiago_LHC: HYPE
TsihTV: maybe change exposure rate on your webcam
ckk0t0: Let’s hear some rhymes
coProof: Thx man for fixing the audio
coProof: Are you still in West P?
JiNJaProductionz: sounds different
codevisionary: there we go
ziggyzergling: amazing
Santiago_LHC: Sounds like IMAX good
JiNJaProductionz: sounds better i guess
codevisionary: now we got the quality
NonTrivial778: bro just use fucking Manjaro, it uses pacman too
Aocuser: Wow! That's better!
princebomin: sounds good
un3okapi: Studio quality.
shekel_gobblin: is that logan pauls old apartment, @georgehotz low key flexing on all us twitchies
z0di4ckx: now is better
ziggyzergling: it's like your in my head
speeddrawing101: shroudInsane
ChanceMakerLIVE: When you stay still you look wonderful just stay still @georgehotz
fuzzuf: Hearing both mics now. Disable the default one.
JiNJaProductionz: @georgehotz very important: why the fuck do i see windows
duzy: u fast as fuck boi
Santiago_LHC: Warp speeds
IsaacRamsay: 1k up 1k down Pog
tanoshiizo: damn, we fast
prakyath_kantharaju: damn bro that is badass
zmechs: wow i feel attacked
Santiago_LHC: My third world internet always sucks
codevisionary: dude I have 90MBPS
codevisionary: what do you mean it sucks???
IsaacRamsay: weird flex but okay
TsihTV: your webcam settings are not right, otherwise stream ok
IsaacRamsay: Kappa
gamecatt: it does but comcast has monopoly here
komocode_: video encoder skipping
NonTrivial778: have you tried Manjaro? its better than archlinux
ckk0t0: Why an echo
Differential: which desktop environment are you gonna use if you do use one?
JiNJaProductionz: stream looks great, no bitrate issues here
BookRaider: did you get fired from comma.ai?
Santiago_LHC: Looks so space-y
Lothsun: Uppers and downers? Who mixes?
NonTrivial778: LUL LUL
Santiago_LHC: DARK MODE
JiNJaProductionz: thank god for that
tanoshiizo: PogChamp
IsaacRamsay: not using dark mode in 2019 WutFace
JiNJaProductionz: your poor eyes on light mode..
cleverclover7: lol
prakyath_kantharaju: arch linux is impossible to use..... shots fired
prakyath_kantharaju: and dark mode FTW
LordDaniel09: lol, he actually installing arch. good luck.
komocode_: video skipping
coProof: What mode is that?
JiNJaProductionz: job security 101
IsaacRamsay: it might be having bitrate issues
codevisionary: Steve Jobs security
NonTrivial778: why the hell do you like xmonad?
dorkmo: zuck em
BookRaider: dont get steve jobbed
jay_al97: oh really, this is awesom
Santiago_LHC: Love the size now
komocode_: would you work for tim cook or steve jobs?
Lothsun: You’ve come to the dark side.
RudeCoffee: Anyone want some smoked meats?
codevisionary: you're making my day George, and I had one hell of a shitty day
risky_banana: risky_banana subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 3 months, currently on a 3 month streak! Light ide theses are for psychos. Love watching you stream man.
Santiago_LHC: I'm always missing the point
duzy: what keyboard do you have atm?
NonTrivial778: Ubuntu doesn't have pacman
jay_al97: u need to create partitions and swap part
jay_al97: then setup file sys
heike1994316: Hi，
JiNJaProductionz: @georgehotz are you doing this so when people ask "What do you do in your spare time?" you can say "Install arch linux"
jay_al97: setup network
JayPouch: hnggggg keeb
codevisionary: pros use Virtualbox, and not VMware
RudeCoffee: How do you know what keys you are pressing?
cleverclover7: i love that you have to type this right now
dxxdpools: I thought you were going to install it on your hard drive ...
Santiago_LHC: Keywords are the best
dorkmo: monitor really big?
heike1994316: Can I talk to you about business？
prakyath_kantharaju: what happened to pixie tech?
Santiago_LHC: Yeah it all looks super small
NonTrivial778: HHK it's all plastic and it costs 200 dollars LUL
akbang47: UEFI is a pain :(
hackyhacks: i'm watching you on arch
dxxdpools: Dual boot
techinicabor: LUL
dxxdpools: No virtual machine
IsaacRamsay: LUL
cleverclover7: lmao
NonTrivial778: LUL LUL LUL LUL
codevisionary: Windows doesn't include default software, it includes default malware
IsaacRamsay: lirikSMART
dxxdpools: Bro no virtual machine
Quad___lol: hi fellow programmer. you look ok-competent. i was thinking you could write me an eshop in PHP - i am planning to sell fish baits. 10$/h. what do you think?
dxxdpools: Dual boot!!!
RudeCoffee: is that chair the new egg?
akbang47: nice fit george ;)
JiNJaProductionz: install arch on your mac LUL
dxxdpools: No
xkcdz: do you guys pronounce it arch or ark?
dxxdpools: Dual boot
codevisionary: @Quad___lol are you serious? I'm your guy
cleverclover7: how big is it?
codevisionary: @Quad___lol pm me
techinicabor: Best FAQ!
coProof: Not enough stamina? Better rebuff
akbang47: LUL
Quad___lol: Kapp
severingwang: he still uses the hhkb keyboard right?
Bogz75: where is your furniture mate
coProof: He can’t do it
techinicabor: "Here are the signs that you should just walk away!"
RudeCoffee: the only linux I have messed with in different versions of ubuntu, so this is unknown waters for me
samosasauce8: How does "installing arch linux have over 100 viewers"
dxxdpools: Dual boot like a man
ziggyzergling: lmao
nuketesty: en us
prakyath_kantharaju: that is a long list
prakyath_kantharaju: bro
NonTrivial778: LUL LUL
dorkmo: lol arch def not for consumer use
jay_al97: search for US
Quad___lol: what are your thoughts on john mcaffee @georgehotz
heike1994316: I love you
akbang47: LOL
xkcdz: Arch or Ark?
heike1994316: A genius
luhartt: luhartt subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 4 months!
RudeCoffee: omg, moving to fast for me to keep up. I will have to rewatch this as a vod
severingwang: what keyboard does he use?
codevisionary: no GUI bruh?
bryanftw29: los angelese
jay_al97: chose the closer to u
techinicabor: Antarctica PogChamp
Hamled: it's Los Angeles
magician2378: los angeles
hackyhacks: @severingwang happy hacking keyboard pro 2
Hamled: that's the official
coProof: tzinfo
Quad___lol: arch linux is just a meme, accept it
nuketesty: tijuana of course
bhad: Wheres the installer gui?
codevisionary: LOL
Bogz75: lel
dorkmo: crazy gf johnny depp
P0LY: LUL
dxxdpools: Georgehotz = legend
coProof: Los_Angeles!
Pyrohair17: Thats a nice home
techinicabor: hooo boy fdisk
coProof: Duh!
jay_al97: sda, sdb ,sdc are devices
codevisionary: how much does your place cost?
jay_al97: sda1,sda2 are partions
IsaacRamsay: dynamic PogChamp
NonTrivial778: if you install Xmonad, please don't install any haskell packet from pacman, just ghc.
coProof: Yeah sda is disc
ejmason101: lsblk
coProof: This is dangerous
jason_rm: i forget why Arch wiki recommends fdisk, but gdisk is also available
bhad: @georgehotz Why are you choosing to use command line over the gui install?
Bogz75: lel
JiNJaProductionz: linux partitions are sysadmin 101, god george
techinicabor: i may or may not have installed another DIY Linux once and stopped at attempting to getting a window manager going, stuff broke pretty hard
napkats: virtual box has had dynamic storage for a while
ejmason101: TBH installing arch by hand teaches you a lot about linux and the different commands that you will run into if you choose to use linux
pyythonn: nah
Pyrohair17: move to the cloud?
cleverclover7: raid
techinicabor: stuff broke to the point where i couldn't get grub to actually do things for itself and i had to constantly specify the kernel and ramdisk
ejmason101: lvm
jay_al97: no
jason_rm: first time? i'd stay away from LVM or RAID
techinicabor: fun time
codevisionary: I had a dream about revolutionizing serverless cloud infrastructure, and then I woke up and I was like, damn... that was all fake? FML.
ejmason101: yes
napkats: install gentoo Kappa
pyythonn: Raid
JiNJaProductionz: you only have a single virtual drive so not raid
jay_al97: it slows down the sys
dorkmo: louis vutton?
Santiago_LHC: My grandma uses LVM
napkats: lul
Pyrohair17: why not raid?
techinicabor: I should've gone with Arch
napkats: yea arch docs are great
tisd_: partition with gdisk
magician2378: you have uefi. if you dont I would be really surprised
napkats: if a noob like me can install arch
dorkmo: jbod
jay_al97: all u need is 2 partitions
Protoxus: Protoxus subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 3 months! Hello H A C K E R M A N
Banakaigames: how u a Linux master and not know about the arch wiki
dxxdpools: How are drivers on arch?
coProof: This is turning into a@meme
bhad: yes
Differential: yes
tisd_: yes
emi1ie: yes
IsaacRamsay: ^
tisd_: use gdisk
ejmason101: n
NonTrivial778: cfdisk
codevisionary: you seem 200ms slower than usual George. Have you been taking something? Just kidding, I'm not your parents
bhad: @codevisionary this is him being slower? wtf
coProof: Ofc
napkats: ^ yea wtf
codevisionary: yes
Santiago_LHC: LOL
IsaacRamsay: fun fact LUL
napkats: famous fo rwat LUL
tanoshiizo: LUL
Pyrohair17: does he live in jersey?
NonTrivial778: LUL LUL LUL that guy is a freaking genius!!!
techinicabor: RedrumFS
dorkmo: pizzagate
codevisionary: @bhad have you seen his self driving coding videos?
bhad: @codevisionary no
codevisionary: @bhad guy types and moves like 100mph
NonTrivial778: see this https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mIrMVPnxa04 freaking genius
coProof: Mmmm ext4
chancechants: ouch
napkats: good purchase...
dxxdpools: What are you drinking?
techinicabor: Known for: RaiserFS, murder
Santiago_LHC: Very amateur moves
Banakaigames: what a nice guy
napkats: ^
princebomin: LMFAOOOOOO
austin_1_2: danD
napkats: @techinicabor LUL
tisd_: cant use ext4 on efi partition
jay_al97: it's recomended
minichota: why does this man have to stream at night. hes the best streamer
tisd_: use fat
Tyoo_: mr broadcaster that is a very nice kitchen
napkats: @minichota you can always catch the vods :(
Banakaigames: reiserFs is totally killer
NonTrivial778: George would you kill your wife if she cheats on you?
dorkmo: WW3
chancechants: lol
minichota: Vods arent as fun
TheCarefulExplorer: its 6:45 AM at my place, just woke up :)
Santiago_LHC: "American computer programmer, entrepreneur, and convicted murderer" isn't that a sweet bio
dxxdpools: How fast can you type?
dxxdpools: Wpm?
minichota: 5wpm
coProof: Yes you need swap partition to be active on the cloud
napkats: youre going to want to uncomment most of those to get the fastest results when youre installing packages
codevisionary: @dxxdpools I'd have to estimate, about 142wpm
dxxdpools: I agree
NonTrivial778: LUL LUL LUL LUL
dxxdpools: @codevisionary
Santiago_LHC: Love that HTML4
Hamled: @georgehotz use the script that checks ping times for a specific list of countries. it's further down the wiki
napkats: good ol wayback machine
fooblaht: Do you know if it’s possible for an enthusiast to get Android Automotive running on real hardware?
Santiago_LHC: Reiser raised money
UniversalGeneve: @georgehotz any thoughts on AI engineering/future of AI?
NonTrivial778: LUL
2knucklechamp: Yooo u need to stream more
BryanSWAGBEAST: hi what are you doing today? :)
IsaacRamsay: LUL
bhad: whats wrong with iran cmonBruh
xkcdz: You should stream on DLive
Banakaigames: it's always cool to me how such smart people like this guy can also be completely insane
duzy: ANELE
coProof: Ctrl^x it
Tyoo_: ANELE WHY DELETE ME
dxxdpools: What wallpaper will you use?
napkats: lol
codevisionary: George, if you stay on Twitch, I guarantee your viewership will continue to pay for your kitchen, for all eternity. Please stay on Twitch forever. Thanks bruh
tisd_: whats wrong with iran yes tell us
BryanSWAGBEAST: hey guys what is he doing
hackyhacks: where's the unix beard
IsaacRamsay: @Banakaigames its because were insane we pull this stuff off lirikSMART
napkats: @codevisionary i doubt it
RudeCoffee: Will tesla make fully automatic autopilot by the end of the year?
AideTechBot: inside out LUL
Santiago_LHC: "cooking stuff"
jurodiwy_777: holy shit
codevisionary: I do, if it involves code
RudeCoffee: kk
napkats: pasta :D
tanoshiizo: do it
emi1ie: yes
capjackm: that would be awesome
capjackm: you should do it high
xkcdz: good content
dxxdpools: ✋🏼
mikey9988: LULW
Banakaigames: I'd watch
Tyoo_: you do options trading george?
xkcdz: Elon bluffs with Tunnels
dxxdpools: Starlink!
techinicabor: Starliiiink
xkcdz: Bitcooonnnect
Banakaigames: I think Elon actually just is into the space thing and self driving is his side hustle
svmihar: are you using a hhkb?
dxxdpools: Neurolink!!!
techinicabor: Hans was looking at selling the company but it just poofed
duzy: yes he is @svmihar
BryanSWAGBEAST: whats Arch Linux?
kevin99gh: @georgehotz can u hack ppls just by knowing there twitch name squadS i was thinking of not behaving but idk if it worth it NotLikeThis
codevisionary: NotLikeThis
Santiago_LHC: @Banakaigames I would also be into the space thing if I had a bunch of badass rockets
svmihar: oh yes dat keyboard dome sound tho.
dorkmo: iran time zone plz
svmihar: it's tingling
lithiumx4900: lithiumx4900 subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months! nice. arch linux. love it
kevin99gh: ill behave lol
dxxdpools: He can hack you just by seeing your face
kevin99gh: lool
coProof: Wtf is a chroot
Banakaigames: i installed Debian once 😎
codevisionary: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cdXYz268rPc < these was the days
dxxdpools: No you are
jay_al97: You need to try black Arch
kevin99gh: he makes hacking look beautiful SeriousSloth
gazny: Arch, Gentoo, Slackware and Void are all cool in their own way
pau1riddle: It is going to break without locale, I suspect
svmihar: what vm is he using?
Hamled: @georgehotz you need en_US.UTF8 at least
RudeCoffee: RudeCoffee is gifting 5 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 5 in the channel!
RudeCoffee: RudeCoffee gifted a Tier 1 sub to Scriddy458!
RudeCoffee: RudeCoffee gifted a Tier 1 sub to TheCellarDoor!
RudeCoffee: RudeCoffee gifted a Tier 1 sub to Caene!
RudeCoffee: RudeCoffee gifted a Tier 1 sub to SomeForeignGuy!
RudeCoffee: RudeCoffee gifted a Tier 1 sub to seniorkae!
dxxdpools: Virtual box?
codevisionary: nice
xkcdz: does he have HHKB lite2 ?
joker2k999: sup guys
chancechants: its loopback
kevin99gh: oooo
chancechants: its for logging
chancechants: and debugging
joker2k999: shoutOut to RudeCoffee
Banakaigames: I want to do void at some point but I don't have a extra machine to do it
chancechants: if your net goes out you can compare against localhost
austin_1_2: Loopback
NonTrivial778: do you use nmcli with Xmonad to connect to wifi?
codevisionary: the more subs, the more likely George will stream often
princebomin: Hey Rudecoffe can i get a sub gift
codevisionary: too bad I'm poor af
death_gadget: grub
dxxdpools: When are you making your own OS @georgehotz
techinicabor: choices, my weakness!
bkolev1: grub!
gazny: grub2 is always good
jay_al97: grup
prakyath_kantharaju: grub ftw
pau1riddle: Install EFI stub
BookRaider: fuck gbbrup
NonTrivial778: @codevisionary he have a job, he is pretty busy always so no LUL
codevisionary: true @NonTrivial778
codevisionary: just dreaming my dreams ...
Banakaigames: normie grub2
gazny: use pacman
SomeForeignGuy: i only know grub 2, do something else so I don't have too
NonTrivial778: pacman -S grub-install
jay_al97: grup-install and the package name
stale2000: MrDestructoid
robn5: can you use pacman without a locale?
robn5: lol nvm guess you can
Hamled: I think lots of stuff defaults to en_US @robn5
Banakaigames: did u know pacman was originally called puckman but the creators of arch thought that it would be too easy to deface
dxxdpools: Lol
Tyoo_: now THAT is a fun fact
Hamled: but iirc you'll get warnings at least from Perl and stuff
dxxdpools: Ok Scott
JonThomasK: whats up mr hotz
pau1riddle: I remember when I was first installing arch on UEFI system, was afraid of bricking it.
pau1riddle: I heard it's possible
Hamled: I've done it with rEFInd as the bootloader
Bloodspark_: yeah I hear the police Kapps
NonTrivial778: first arch linux problems
el_pirulote: Apple User using Arch OMEGALUL
codevisionary: it's not possible to brick a system either unless your hardware is locked
NonTrivial778: its just the grub
Bloodspark_: OMEGALUL
dxxdpools: Startx lol
mikey9988: windows PogChamp
Banakaigames: the police coming to get hotz cause he such an elite haxer
mikey9988: monkaS ^
NonTrivial778: its the shitty grub.conf thing LUL
gazny: I have to install grub targeting the disk. sudo grub-install /dev/sdX
austin_1_2: Go back to settings in hyper v
khuonguts: sounds like a new keyboard lol
JonThomasK: grub hub
codevisionary: nah, it's just that his mic is sitting on his desk, too many vibrations
Knarez: whats he doing with arch lol
pau1riddle: @codevisionary yeah, but I had to mess with my firmware to disable the safe boot, set the motherboard password, change device boot order, all while knowing there's windows 10 UEFI stuff which messes with my linux stuff and overwrites it
Santiago_LHC: Guys, he needs a million instagram followers. http://1m2019.com
gazny: Of course geo, you can do everything
NonTrivial778: what about os-prober?
NonTrivial778: use cfdisk
mikey9988: monkaS @Santiago_LHC
jay_al97: u need to delete it and start again
NonTrivial778: cfdisk is eaasy
pau1riddle: I once resized a partition and lost my data.
codevisionary: @pau1riddle that's monopolistic corporate behavior at it's finest. That's why I hate everything proprietary.
NonTrivial778: yeah you can't resized
IsaacRamsay: ceezMT
dxxdpools: You are human!!
capjackm: you don't post enough on instagram
MrBankster: fun times!
NonTrivial778: noooo
dxxdpools: I was about to say robot
codevisionary: I used to respect Lenovo until they made a shitty deal with Microsoft. Now I'm selling my Lenovo laptop.
pau1riddle: @codevisionary I also heard some laptops have protection against installing linux on firmware level.
codevisionary: yeah, Lenovo does now
dxxdpools: @codevisionary when was this?
Banakaigames: shitty laptops
mikey9988: monkaS @pau1riddle
JonThomasK: me
gazny: Pretty sure we had it if we just used Parted
Banakaigames: I have a Lenovo Linux laptop 👨🌾
dxxdpools: ✋🏼
ahahaitslit: yee boi
ad5k: Today’s cloud looking good
codevisionary: same here @Banakaigames , luckily we have versions that aren't locked in the bios
NonTrivial778: holy shit
dxxdpools: 🤛🏼🤓🤜🏼 we have your back
codevisionary: the new ones are locked down to Windows OS only
NonTrivial778: my internet speed is really low LUL
bkolev1: Its sectors!
pau1riddle: @georgehotz there is a perfect 6 minute tutorial on installing arch from scratch on youtube. I used it successfuly 2 times.
mikey9988: do you have a external monitor @georgehotz
pau1riddle: @georgehotz specifically for UEFI.
Longboolean: @pau1riddle how many times did you try Kappa
Banakaigames: my last two laptops have been thinkpad 420 and ideaPad 320
tanoshiizo: youtube tutorials aren't fun
JonThomasK: ef
092288C: cheer1500 Hi Hotz, just wanted to drop in to thank you for the limera1n tool for my iPod Touch back in 2010. Good luck on your Arch Linux install.
jay_al97: no
dxxdpools: He is the tutorial
JonThomasK: EFI (Fat) >
mr_rackman: installing ARCH what kind of meme shit is this
austin_1_2: My favorite tutorials are the ones with foreigners with broken English Kappa
Banakaigames: I like this stream cause u do a lot of things I do only like 10 times faster
codevisionary: ^
Banakaigames: at least it's not gentoo
khuonguts: I am noooob here, why does he need to do this?
092288C: it's a fun project
NonTrivial778: emerge fucking sucks with their stupid flags
Sylens__: Why arch Linux?
austin_1_2: Fedora is the best
RFP_Hybrid: noone knows Kappa
austin_1_2: Kappa
TechieRS: everyone i know in iran uses it
dxxdpools: So he can hack arch
NonTrivial778: Kappa
TechieRS: i know no one there :)
codevisionary: LUL @TechieRS
JonThomasK: so meta
tanoshiizo: LUL
mr_rackman: ya arch got really popular in iran after stuxnet Kappa
Bloodspark_: LUL
EXSNarrow: Should've stuck to Iran LUL
JonThomasK: rip Groff
gazny: lmao, did we not mount sda2?
el_pirulote: nihilism ResidentSleeper ResidentSleeper ResidentSleeper
Meanstreak: @georgehotz must've come from Iran last time
Banakaigames: who TF is groff
092288C: @Banakaigames https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w8EKH_fjmXA
gazny: ty geo
Longboolean: "nothing in life needs to be done" groff fails to download, you brought this on yourself Kappa
JonThomasK: lol
092288C: green tea is the way to go
techinicabor: may or may not be watching from VR in bed now
NonTrivial778: nice clean apartment
CaptainRoberts: tea or coffee?
ejmason101: ls --color=auto
pewjewpie: im sorry, what r we doing?
nuketesty: installing doom on linux
RFP_Hybrid: nothing Kappa
codevisionary: https://clips.twitch.tv/TransparentTangentialSkirretPipeHype
Banakaigames: if u were really being optimal your computer would be closer to the fridge
pewjewpie: tks nuke
noctrnalmachine: how long you going to be on for?
bhad: Whats taking so long hurry up
davidsit_site: it's "like" arch
JonThomasK: grub>
Longboolean: NotLikeThis
092288C: You're getting close at least
hackyhacks: did you make the config file?
JonThomasK: look left?
noctrnalmachine: if it were easy, it wouodnt be fun/challenging
CraftyGaming: "I look behind the painting"
techinicabor: this was my Gentoo experience LUL
JonThomasK: attack?
Incurs0: LUL
jay_al97: u need to install the kernel as well
092288C: LUL
Longboolean: LUL
slim_bhris: sudo apt install windows
el_pirulote: KFC?
ziggyzergling: LUL
NonTrivial778: you need to use os-prober
pau1riddle: @georgehotz there's 6 minute tutorial on youtube, just follow that
hackyhacks: grub-mkconfig > /boot/grub/grub.cfg
noctrnalmachine: literally hkw i learned linux....except at night after id get off of work
E_Pizza: arch is user friendly, honest KaRappa
onu4r: that desperate tone
Banakaigames: I'm glad I'm not the only one who's this lost when I get to this screen
techinicabor: you literally have to go like kernel /dev/sda/where-the-kernel-is and same for initramfs
davidsit_site: obviously you need to pick up the red key which you can't see
gazny: Think we failed to install the grub boot loader to the location of the drive
JonThomasK: grub> hub
NonTrivial778: LUL LUL LUL
Banakaigames: I've had this exact experience updating my kernel
Mibbzy: Woah new place?
Gtxgaming23: is this a speed test installation?
NonTrivial778: i think you need to update
Longboolean: has anyone done an arch install speed run? Kappa
techinicabor: heck yes
squidlytoads: > bob
techinicabor: i believe there are arch speedruns.
Longboolean: LUL
ejmason101: "ls -la --color=auto"
NonTrivial778: install xorg and xmonad xmonad xmonad
jay_al97: install a desktop environment
gazny: Lets get some larbs in here
samosasauce8: what mouse and keyboard does he use
jackdaniels7474: Yo geohot wat u drinking?
Sublimus7: !uptime
codevisionary: @jackdaniels7474 green tea
jay_al97: which $SHELL
Longboolean: at least he says it is green tea
favsfn: !cpu
Knarez: install network manager Kappa
codevisionary: try the stuff, try it warm. I'm on it right now man. It's good shit.
NonTrivial778: wifi-menu
jay_al97: use nmuti
Knarez: nmtui
NonTrivial778: nmcli or wifi-menu
jay_al97: or nmcli
Crying_Potato: everytime he streams hes in a new mansion
pau1riddle: but how can you install if you have no internet
092288C: you didn't install gnome-network-manager, right?
codevisionary: @Crying_Potato I'm pretty sure most of the time he's in a closet somewhere
davidsit_site: 😆
r00tdk: Ifconfig eth0 up
brute505_: ifconfig eth0 up
slim_bhris: service network-manager restart
NonTrivial778: ifconfig is in netutils
pau1riddle: ifconfig is deprecated and arch doesn't have it
shrek_361: ip l set (interface) up
JonThomasK: set
lsx_daniel: what keyboard are you using XD
NonTrivial778: HHK pro 2
Hamled: @georgehotz IP link set eth0 up
JonThomasK: we did it
techinicabor: We've entered the series of tubes
brute505_: PogChamp
Sublimus7: Pog
bhad: with chats help
092288C: PogChamp
davidsit_site: why install deprecated tools instead of learning new things? @78
lsx_daniel: WHAT KEYBOARD its sounds nice
brute505_: @davidsit_site if it aint broke dont fix it
Tazalpha: whats up
codevisionary: they still do in Ubuntu, don't they?
shrek_361: systemctl
NonTrivial778: geohot u need to start programming in Python no more time to install arch Kappa
Banakaigames: 5/30 the day George fixed the internet
JonThomasK: pacman -S zsh
jay_al97: yes
Knarez: ye
davidsit_site: back in my day.....
Bloodspark_: back in my day Kappa
Sainfuw: install zsh
Hamled: yeah
lsx_daniel: I must know the KEYBOARD Kreygasm
092288C: Ubuntu is very bloated
mr_rackman: those are gateron silent brown switches and i refuse to be corrected
jay_al97: install a Desktop env
pau1riddle: you should pacman -Syu
lsx_daniel: arch linux vs manjaro linux lol
clapsnowman881: make an alias
NonTrivial778: pacman sucks with Haskell packages
bkolev1: you need some i3 rice
gazny: Just add it to your .bashrc file or .zshrc
Knarez: -Syuu
NonTrivial778: use tldr tool, pacman -S tldr
NonTrivial778: LUL
Banakaigames: now u can install Firefox and use it to download an Ubuntu iso Kappa
lsx_daniel: @georgehotz I must KNOW the Keyboard Kreygasm
chancechants: alias ls='ls --color=auto'
davidsit_site: vote for bashrc file
Hamled: @georgehotz the y is download newest PKG list
lsx_daniel: @Banakaigames lmao
techinicabor: i'm liking Arch the more i see it
chancechants: ~/.bashrc
prakyath_kantharaju: Can we use ROS in Arch.. IF so I am moving to Arch from ubuntu ?
NonTrivial778: We NEED XMONAD!
shrek_361: you need to rice i3 gaps and set up urxvt with tabs.
Cube_Is_Life20: hey george how hard was it to secure investor funding for ,ai?
092288C: @georgehotz What's the keyboard you're using?
r00tdk: Bashrc
lsx_daniel: WE MUST KNOW THE KEYBOARD Kreygasm
Knarez: arch's /bin/sh is symlinkd to bash Kappa
prakyath_kantharaju: source bashrc
NonTrivial778: @092288C HHKB Pro 2
prakyath_kantharaju: bro
gazny: oh, you are a root user, make a normal user
jay_al97: which $SHELL
techinicabor: LUL
092288C: @NonTrivial778 thanks
svmihar: which bash
mr_rackman: YO GEORGE is that the version with electrocapacitive switches
svmihar: which $shell
codevisionary: one day @georgehotz will hire me, and I will have purpose
Sublimus7: is this to start hacking the simulation?
r00tdk: Export SHELL=/bin/bash
chancechants: gg
UniversalGeneve: nice
NonTrivial778: XORG XORG we need xorg
gazny: Install LARBS!
092288C: Install i3
Differential: desktop environment?
shrek_361: i3 gaps!
tanoshiizo: window manager
tanoshiizo: ops
NonTrivial778: XORG startx
Knarez: bspwm time
Banakaigames: vim homie
pau1riddle: install X or Wayland
Longboolean: install cowsay Kappa
gazny: curl -LO larbs.xyz/larbs.sh sh larbs.sh
hackyhacks: it's a tiling wm
Sainfuw: try to install rvm, i fail on that :(
luhartt: i3 gaps
UniversalGeneve: play a game LUL
davidsit_site: python
NonTrivial778: i3 is horrible
tanoshiizo: i3 is good
092288C: default i3 is horrible
zitkolong9999: try sway on wayland
jay_al97: install space-vim
onlyfollowstupidstreamer: do backflip
hackyhacks: install a AUR tool
chancechants: now install ubuntu
codevisionary: is comma AI taking any applicants? @georgehotz
slim_bhris: install cmatrix
Banakaigames: install gentoo
pau1riddle: I'm on wayland right now, it works
NonTrivial778: do you use simplestfloat in Xmonad and doCenterFloat ?
NonTrivial778: LUL
gazny: Just use tmux
techinicabor: i tried installing wayland when i installed gentoo
techinicabor: the login prompt just kept going in circles
davidsit_site: can we agree python? ....@codevisionary yeah. I have been having fun with one of their datasets
Mibbzy: why don't you just main arch linux?
gazny: https://wiki.archlinux.org/index.php/Sway
Mibbzy: No I mean like as your actual OS instead of vm
NonTrivial778: install awesome wm !!
Mibbzy: fuck windows
NonTrivial778: do you use conky with Xmonad george?
Banakaigames: the ghosts always go a predictable pattern
NonTrivial778: its written in Lua
xaaaaaaaxd: hi
TheCellarDoor: sway is i3 for wayland
r00tdk: Hello from india
Knarez: bspwm masterrace
NonTrivial778: i3 is in C
JonThomasK: should be written in rust
Hamled: @georgehotz would like to see Wayland get setup. I used X11 when I set up my Arch box, but I'm thinking of switching
TheCellarDoor: yes
Longboolean: should be written in NodeJS Kappa
NonTrivial778: i3 is easier to config than Xmonad
Knarez: not for any good reason
NonTrivial778: Xmonad config is all in haskell
davidsit_site: connect to your arch from WSL to display apps over x11 ssh. secure keys. or wh
onu4r: tmux tmux tmux
NonTrivial778: i3 is just text
zitkolong9999: i3 gaps is like ubuntu for wm, a lot of people use it.
JonThomasK: im a expert in full stack. I know nodejs so well /s
davidsit_site: meh. that was an incomplete thought
halabalu: Hi! How about to try Windows subsystem for linux? Why do u need Arch? Sorry I am to late asking.
NonTrivial778: xmonad.hs from 6 years ago omg
abhb09: Why you don’t do any CTF stuff?
jay_al97: do u ever watch Live over flow
onu4r: @abhb09 he's retired
Mibbzy: @halabalu I agree
Bloodspark_: WutFace sound
chancechants: lol
JonThomasK: no
pau1riddle: It's custom DSL
Knarez: it's the i3 confg shit, disgusting plain text
davidsit_site: do you not like unsafe memory @jonthomask or do you like rust for another reason
c19946: its not yml
mikey9988: dsl Kreygasm
JonThomasK: i was memein on new hotness
jay_al97: may be u need to install linux-headers
keuger: anyone knows what keyboard george is using?
Banakaigames: since u installed arch u might be smart enough for Rick And Morty now
LDRAR: hhkb
Bloodspark_: does anyone hear that sound too?
toolegit2quit_: HHKB
keuger: thankyou
JonThomasK: maybe its Swag
keuger: sounds awesome!
halabalu: @Bloodspark_ me 2
Bloodspark_: @halabalu ah so it's not ony me okay
Bloodspark_: only*
Longboolean: thats the sound of progress my friend
092288C: HHKB sounds awesome, but so expensive for a new one
Haffa: anyone know why we are installing arch linux?
Bloodspark_: !keyboard
092288C: Prolly just stick with my Model M
techinicabor: nice broken error text!
Banakaigames: ask not why but why not
gazny: Dont run it as root
onu4r: @haffa for fun
Haffa: ahh ok. thats good enough reason for me :)
techinicabor: would love to use my Model M but i'm good with using this MX Blue'd keyboard until it dies
Bloodspark_: MrDestructoid
halabalu: @Banakaigames why not Gentoo?
davidsit_site: goodnight gents
pau1riddle: maybe you have to install gpu driver
Bloodspark_: we don't?
Knarez: bspwm > i3
archeadis: go bspwm
Banakaigames: tfw no gee pee you
Enoxx__: hi
hackyhacks: pacman -S sx
IndoPridePinoy: i'm not sure but if you shutdown the VM. you should be able to enable gpu in hyper-v settings
archeadis: it is very much supported
archeadis: bspwm is very popular
hackyhacks: also, pacman -S org-xinit
Longboolean: LUL
JonThomasK: pacman -tSla
stanleyderlurch1337: add hardware
Banakaigames: just download more RAM
machinelearningbot: ^
gazny: Depending on your intel cpu you can pass the intel Igpu to a vm
NonTrivial778: HHKB its pure plastic and has a shitty switches that feels like a mix of membrane and brown cherry mx, and it costs 200 dollars
slim_bhris: download a gpu
dragan2271: hi bro
Bloodspark_: MrDestructoid
Banakaigames: x gonna give it to ya
momo4885: still study unity?
JonThomasK: swag
NonTrivial778: why no music Geohot?
techinicabor: aw yeaaaa
NonTrivial778: install terminator
abhb09: @nontrivial778 good recommendation
NonTrivial778: its cool
codevisionary: YES
lilpdf: https://soundcloud.com/fyvrbeats/wwwdot
NonTrivial778: pacman -S terminator LUL
codevisionary: RIP Mac
JonThomasK: Susan Boyle
abhb09: :))))
archeadis: geo are you still following crypto?
Knarez: gotta use ST in 2019 Kappa
pau1riddle: let's listen to uziq or aphex twin
slim_bhris: some lynrd skynrd
techinicabor: ooo
Bloodspark_: SourPls
lilpdf: bangin baus
pau1riddle: dropping frames
JonThomasK: lol
Bloodspark_: LUL
NonTrivial778: LUL LUL LU
archeadis: BSPWM!!
youngmarsh: MrDestructoid
moosezero: moosezero subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Bloodspark_: PogChamp
NonTrivial778: install terminator and tell me if its shit or not LUL
NonTrivial778: you can use killall Xorg
NonTrivial778: LUL
Banakaigames: woah
pau1riddle: add exec i3 to .xinit
Bloodspark_: LUL
ironiiK_: mod enter
techinicabor: LUL
TheCellarDoor: win enter for terminal
gazny: super enter
092288C: Win Enter
zitkolong9999: mod (win) enter
UniversalGeneve: @georgehotz have you ever tried to code in an esoteric language?
icraymer: For what do you use arch linux? greetings from germany :D
092288C: pacman -S xorg
JonThomasK: we need some sense
halo_krs: sup
gazny: Or just change the name there to xterm
Longboolean: guten Tag
092288C: uxterm
gardenweasel: come to brazil
halo_krs: good morning
zitkolong9999: install dmenu also
JonThomasK: i3 is a terrible car
SuperChefJack: hey do you ever stream guitar hero?
samtheprogram: lol what
dxxdpools: Install manjaro
Banakaigames: ^
pau1riddle: install rxvt-unicode
pau1riddle: it is sensible
SuperChefJack: try streaming guitar hero. seems easier than whatever this game is
lossfunction: PogChamp
tanoshiizo: my eyes WutFace
codevisionary: spot on
092288C: chromium
tanoshiizo: chromium
092288C: pacman -S chromium
Knarez: -Ss search
TheCellarDoor: use chromium. google chrome is only in aur
Knarez: -Ss is to search
lossfunction: you can pacman -Ss chrome
Banakaigames: eww chrome
Longboolean: chromium-browser ?
NonTrivial778: chromium
gazny: Lets check our htop
zutchbell: btw i use
092288C: Mod D
r00tdk: Chromium is not chrome
ScrubLifeChoseMe: monkaS
092288C: Mod (Win) D, then search what program you want
pau1riddle: launchis is with dmenu
codevisionary: @georgehotz you might want to go ahead and clone that VM, just in-case you run into a brick wall
gazny: geo chuckwm is a lot like i3
Knarez: use dmenu, and fuck i3 use bspwm Kappa
paul7115: arch i3wm = purrfection
NonTrivial778: Google Chrome will ban adblock users soon
risky_banana: I use the AOL browser that came on my pre-installed HP :)
archeadis: use bspwm
r00tdk: Hello george from india
092288C: you can also use the i3 config to set shortcuts to launch programs
Banakaigames: install Microsoft edge Kappa
Haffa: LUL
Haffa: gbuttTrap
codevisionary: LUL
pau1riddle: it errors out
techinicabor: I'll wait and see how they go about banning adblock before abandoning it, probably for Chredge LUL
risky_banana: Edge does run Chromium... sooo that joke kinda works
codevisionary: @NonTrivial778 are you serious though?
codevisionary: @NonTrivial778 I will hate Google forever if they do that
Banakaigames: ya the new edge is available for Linux I think
zitkolong9999: You might want to reconfig those shortcut, switch windows in i3 is oddly annoying for vim user (1 key off)
JonThomasK: LUL
Bloodspark_: MrDestructoid
tanoshiizo: LUL
gazny: log out and log in as new user
JonThomasK: :O
r00tdk: Export DISPLAY=:0
MrBankster: you are a wizard
r00tdk: Do this
gazny: root user is controlling the xorg server need to log out
codevisionary: https://www.androidpolice.com/2019/05/29/google-still-plans-to-kill-chromes-existing-adblock-apis/ < holy shit. No.
JonThomasK: i own the cookie
jakeypaulyguyy: ur awesome
NonTrivial778: I use all in float layout
techinicabor: crunchy interference
pau1riddle: You login as new user and start i3
jakeypaulyguyy: cheer30
bcrscahh198987: why are you installing arch linux
Banakaigames: he's already did he's install chromium now
paul7115: What Is the purpose of Microsoft Windows? To install Linux virtual machine
pau1riddle: have to use xinit
JonThomasK: permission to eat the cookie
pau1riddle: add exec i3 to ~/.xinitrc
lossfunction: LUL
ironiiK_: sandbox escapes OUT
NonTrivial778: Geohot just use Manjaro its almost the same, the installation its easier and you can't choose the window manager before
bcrscahh198987: Archlinux is only keep what you need
robn5: you're gonna love it when an update breaks your install
codevisionary: BREAKING NEWS: https://clips.twitch.tv/OriginalTemperedWolverineBCWarrior
gazny: pretty sure geo wants to learn, not have it done for him
bcrscahh198987: Archlinux is great for tinkering
gazny: did we add our user to the wheel group?
bcrscahh198987: You're in the bay area right?
spawn2056: Manjaro saves you from all this (even though this tinkering can be fun of course)
lossfunction: PogChamp
ironiiK_: sandbox with 777 on /root .. uhhh
NonTrivial778: LUL
slim_bhris: 666 lol
mlgdotca: does he play league
JonThomasK: hotz prefers 666
jakeypaulyguyy: 666
Banakaigames: now don't leave install temple OS
NonTrivial778: u always run chrome in a sandbox LUL I never did that
Longboolean: TheIlluminati
codevisionary: Geo, you should build a browser out of Chromium
NonTrivial778: git clone chromium LUL
jakeypaulyguyy: port chromium to wii
mikey9988: LUL
mikey9988: temple os
bcrscahh198987: temple OS rofl
gazny: some holy C
092288C: TEMPLEOS PogChamp
NonTrivial778: LUL LUL LUL
stysMMaker: PogChamp
bcrscahh198987: Try menuetOS
092288C: @stysMMaker TriHard 7
gazny: Yes to temple os!
stysMMaker: TriHard
halo_krs: firefoxium
tanoshiizo: cooking stream when?
lilpdf: SingsNote SingsNote
r00tdk: Go to sleep
lilpdf: night baus
NonTrivial778: you'll switch to i3?
Banakaigames: is the cloud heaven
abhb09: CTF CTF
NonTrivial778: holy shit that font is horrible
jay_al97: Im surprised u sleep at 11
TheCellarDoor: check out qtile, it's written and hackable in python
SpaceGhost8: chromium uber alles LUL
Banakaigames: no Firefox just made new renderer didn't they
gazny: You can in i3, check out Dwm it has what you want it to do
092288C: you can do resizing without touching the mouse
NonTrivial778: Awesome wm is perfect for you then!!!
abhb09: CTF CTF
NonTrivial778: LUL
JonThomasK: l key
TheCellarDoor: mod r
r00tdk: Ctf ctf ctf ctf ctf
abhb09: CTF CTF CTF
jakeypaulyguyy: why is python slow
pau1riddle: Enter resize mode and use hjkl
Knarez: bspwm, easiest bash config
bcrscahh198987: because it's not compiled
NonTrivial778: def main: __asm__
NonTrivial778: LUL
bcrscahh198987: Python is JIT now
lilpdf: Now this is streaming
092288C: @georgehotz https://unix.stackexchange.com/questions/255344/resizing-windows-in-i3-using-keyboard-only configure i3
jakeypaulyguyy: don't u just compile it then
bcrscahh198987: Python "compiling" isn't the same as C/C compiling
abhb09: pwn2own
gazny: Install both and decide
Knarez: can change the config a bit and not have to enter a "mode"
jay_al97: u can map that to vim keys
JonThomasK: basic vim
lilpdf: night
Knarez: LOL I guess it is a rabbit hole but still
TheAmazingCaptain: GEOORRGGEEE do you mind giving my sweet piece of man meat DORIAN a shout out... KEYWORD: DORIAN
TheAmazingCaptain: my friend DORIAN fought in iraq
TheAmazingCaptain: on the iraqi side
jay_al97: have u tried space-vim?
NonTrivial778: how you are able to sleep always at the same hour ? LUL
techinicabor: LUL
092288C: LUL
TheAmazingCaptain: keyword dorian
Bloodspark_: D:
jakeypaulyguyy: make a script to auto change scripts so you don't have to every time you reinstall
SpaceGhost8: asdf
zitkolong9999: neovim spacevim
NonTrivial778: NO TABS! TABS = SPACE GEOHOT!!!
jakeypaulyguyy: config*
Banakaigames: if u wanna learn vim just do vimtutor
Knarez: edit your .Xresource file now for colors
Knarez: Kappa
NonTrivial778: now start coding a SLAM I give you 3 hours
TheAmazingCaptain: george
archeadis: when next stream
TheAmazingCaptain: would you consider yourself a twink or a bear
bcrscahh198987: try rm *
gazny: Just imagine on a real machine that has a gpu
092288C: Mod Shift Q
gazny: ^
Bombapil0t: gg
Banakaigames: idk I see him as an otter I think he'd generate a lot of power
Longboolean: "never change the defaults" --> "default colors are terrible" Kappa
NonTrivial778: why do you still have windows install in that computer?
pau1riddle: Ctrl d
NonTrivial778: Kappa
thodeann: why i3 when sway exist
Knarez: defaults on most everything are garbage
thodeann: wayland one
TheAmazingCaptain: george do the blindfolded arch linux install challenge
092288C: LUL
NonTrivial778: LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL
codevisionary: goodnight @georgehotz . Don't forget to export your VM to backup, and eat your vegetables
gazny: Steaming as root
TheAmazingCaptain: blindfolded arch linux challenge is a tasty game
JonThomasK: try Swag
bcrscahh198987: what about gentoo
Bloodspark_: lol
JonThomasK: lol
TheAmazingCaptain: george can i log in to your root ;)
SpaceGhost8: true LUL
jay_al97: lol
2bumbum: hahaha
Hamled: @georgehotz What do you think makes a good CTF reversing challenge? I was looking at creating one for OpenCTF (probably next year... it's getting late)
jakeypaulyguyy: yes
TheAmazingCaptain: no george i dont want to log into this
TheAmazingCaptain: i want to log into u
NonTrivial778: Gentoo uses emerge and its awful than pacman LUL
TheAmazingCaptain: give me the keys to your heart
Banakaigames: arch is actually good Gentoo is a meme
092288C: 127.0.0.1 6969
mikey9988: monkaS
jo_renttt: monkaW
codevisionary: who just rejects the opportunity to login to a VM in George's kitchen?
TheAmazingCaptain: you remind me of if terry a. davis had a cool nephew who he hung out with at thanksgiving some years
nokinobi: also you can install polybar
NonTrivial778: implement this in python using Gnuplot https://dcc.fceia.unr.edu.ar/sites/default/files/uploads/materias/fruchterman.pdf you can do it in less than 30 min for sure LUL
092288C: Arch User Repository
092288C: A.U.R.
markovchain21: @georgehotz i love python, but is c > python ?
TheAmazingCaptain: try installing wii u on your computer
zitkolong9999: install yay for aur
TheAmazingCaptain: dual boot into miiverse mfer
jakeypaulyguyy: dolphin emulator
Hamled: @georgehotz What do you think makes a good CTF reversing challenge? I was looking at creating one for OpenCTF
codevisionary: there's a wii emu?
jakeypaulyguyy: ya
JonThomasK: bye god
Banakaigames: for Wii u it's CEMU dolphin is Wii
Bloodspark_: Dolphin 🐬
gazny: Church when?
jakeypaulyguyy: How long
TheAmazingCaptain: george how do you think you will die
TsihTV: Do you have a roomba
gazny: Saw your talk as sxsw
NonTrivial778: Is this a good paper https://dcc.fceia.unr.edu.ar/sites/default/files/uploads/materias/fruchterman.pdf ?
NonTrivial778: LUL LUL
Bloodspark_: and gamecube
jay_al97: what was ur last CTF
abhb09: CTF
JonThomasK: what kind of shampoo do you use?
Wireballz: Is that a new home ?
TheAmazingCaptain: George. Where do you see yourself in ten years
hackyhacks: when's the next math stream?
bbrak: you like cats?
pau1riddle: why do companies pay for security audits when nobody hacks anybody?
jakeypaulyguyy: install wii on roomba
Appz_x: How much did my EON go up today ?
TheAmazingCaptain: WHY IS YOUR KITCHEN EMPTY
gazny: gggggggggggggggggg
Bombapil0t: :D
jo_renttt: LUL
UniversalGeneve: any paper implementation streams soon?
mikey9988: LUL
TheAmazingCaptain: WHERE IS YOUR FURNITUUUUREEE
092288C: LUL
TheAmazingCaptain: WHERE IS YOUR FURNITURE
Bloodspark_: PogChamp Clap
TheAmazingCaptain: YOU LIVE IN AN EMPTY HOUSE
P0LY: gg :)
UniversalGeneve: lionRapgod
Banakaigames: gg everyone
Bloodspark_: sellout LUL
stysMMaker: LUL
Appz_x: How much did my EON go up today ??
Bombapil0t: don't forget to follow on instagram
NonTrivial778: sellout
slim_bhris: wow i'm impressed
JonThomasK: lol
tanoshiizo: Kappa
lovetaylorswift13: LUL
Bloodspark_: money btw LUL
Longboolean: unless you try to swiffer a carpet Kappa
slim_bhris: faxs
hackyhacks: i'll see you outside the simulation.
JonThomasK: got a MOUSE
jakeypaulyguyy: what sweatshirt? I NEED TO KNOE
tanoshiizo: gamer mouse PogChamp
092288C: LUL
jo_renttt: u have my mouse PogChamp
TheAmazingCaptain: would you ever be willing to work as a personal rent boy
fizeh: HHKB POGCHAMP
youngmarsh: hahahahahahahahaha
slim_bhris: sweater
Bombapil0t: lit
JonThomasK: Pog
jakeypaulyguyy: what sweatshirt
P0LY: Kreygasm
UniversalGeneve: I like the hyperminimalism of your house. don't get furniture
092288C: HHKB is 2/3 of my weekly paycheck
NonTrivial778: do rap
Wireballz: is that a new house ?
JonThomasK: what shampoo @georgehotz
NonTrivial778: A FINAL RAP SONNG
SKPTCL: New home??
NonTrivial778: A FINAL RAPP SOOONG PLEASE
IbraMiharbi: wait what is that keyboard called?
NonTrivial778: RAP RAP RAP RAP
MatiGoG: commercials Pog
edoin21: Cloud Tour pls
mikey9988: LUL
slim_bhris: Kanye look
092288C: @IbraMiharbi Happy Hacking Keyboard
JonThomasK: oh here we go
SKPTCL: SKPTCL subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months!
Banakaigames: i also wear a light grey hoodie I'm literally u
quickfloor: @georgehotz Why do you care about what people think u r ?
IbraMiharbi: @092288C thx
SKPTCL: Twitch Prime for u Hotz
TheAmazingCaptain: are you jewish, and i mean that in a good way
jakeypaulyguyy: also wear a similar hoodie
quickfloor: New Rap ?
UniversalGeneve: lionRapgod
Bloodspark_: haHAA
slim_bhris: fire fire fire
NonTrivial778: lul lul
JonThomasK: fire
fizeh: POG
espionn: BARS
NonTrivial778: LUL LUL LUL
092288C: the next Watsky right here
Landon_1: 🔥
quickfloor: We all are waiting for new rap . new RAP
NonTrivial778: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
gazny: panicBasket panicBasket
jakeypaulyguyy: SOUND CLOUD RAPPER
MrBankster: that flow doe
tanoshiizo: CurseLit
barkazzaz: !albumName
espionn: PATTY
UniversalGeneve: cloud = SD?
gazny: WutFace
slim_bhris: LIL HOTZ
fizeh: KANYE BARS
092288C: LUL
NonTrivial778: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
オレンジ420: Pepega Clap
quickfloor: I hate girls with bf coz they love attention
Banakaigames: wtf 🔥🔥🔥 🔥🔥 🔥🔥 🔥🔥 🔥
JonThomasK: banger
P0LY: PogChamp
NonTrivial778: LUL LUL LUL LUL
sp1der_cat: LUL
youngmarsh: do some bong tokes for the subz
Bloodspark_: bruh LUL
pau1riddle: there's a rap lyrics generator, I saw a link on reddit
NonTrivial778: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
SKPTCL: fk i just got here
mikey9988: LUL
JonThomasK: LUL
TheAmazingCaptain: george can you turn sideways
TheAmazingCaptain: let us get the profile shot
quickfloor: When we could buy your merch ?
JonThomasK: weed agreemet
TheAmazingCaptain: let us get that profile look
jay_al97: i loved ur old album
codevisionary: I came for the clips, as always
lovetaylorswift13: cheers
codevisionary: peace out george
stysMMaker: 👋
SKPTCL: someone upload the archive quick
jakeypaulyguyy: see ya
Longboolean: o/